<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.6">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://192.168.1.68:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://192.168.1.68:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2019-08-04T15:43:58+01:00</updated><id>http://192.168.1.68:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">ethical.chat</title><subtitle>ethical.chat is theshawe's entry in the 2019 Global Fixathon, more tbc soon...</subtitle><author><name>theshawe</name></author><entry><title type="html">Welcome to the fixathon, meet the Ethical.Chat</title><link href="http://192.168.1.68:4000/welcome-to-fixathon-meet-ethical-chat/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Welcome to the fixathon, meet the Ethical.Chat" /><published>2019-08-02T11:11:11+01:00</published><updated>2019-08-02T11:11:11+01:00</updated><id>http://192.168.1.68:4000/welcome-to-fixathon-meet-ethical-chat</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://192.168.1.68:4000/welcome-to-fixathon-meet-ethical-chat/">&lt;h2 id=&quot;introduction&quot;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hey, I’m going to keep this short and sweet, as it’s only Day 01 and I’m posting this to get some content up on the blog! If you’re new, my name is David Shawe and I’m a designer/developer from Belfast, Northern Ireland. I currently reside in Co.Down and I trade as a self employed web designer. I’m entering the Global Online &lt;a href=&quot;https://fixathon.io/&quot;&gt;fixathon&lt;/a&gt; because I believe in the power of positive change and I love watching communities form, grow and make impact. As a group of Tech Impact Makers we intend to fight the Climate Breakdown crisis and I intend to fight that by raising awareness around the conversation of ethics in general. This is only day one and there is a lot of work to do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;ethicalchat&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://ethical.chat&quot;&gt;Ethical.Chat&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This website and blogpost kickstarts my project that I’m calling &lt;a href=&quot;https://ethical.chat&quot;&gt;Ethical.Chat&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m going to blog to my progress during the hackathon. I’m also going to &lt;a href=&quot;https://brew.com/ethicalchat&quot;&gt;podcast&lt;/a&gt; and I’ll probably, well most definitely do a few &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitch.tv/thetheshawe&quot;&gt;twitch&lt;/a&gt; streams. I’ve been wanting to learn to how become a pro with OBS for years. So the now is a perfect excuse to skill up in that area.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Regarding the project and hackathon entry. I have a several different perspectives on how the project will pan out. At the moment all that is concrete is the name.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://ethical.chat&quot;&gt;Ethical.Chat&lt;/a&gt; will be the project that I enter into the &lt;a href=&quot;https://fixathon.io/&quot;&gt;fixathon&lt;/a&gt; with and thank you so much for taking interest.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;fixathon&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://fixathon.io/&quot;&gt;fixathon&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&quot;https://fixathon.io/&quot;&gt;fixathon&lt;/a&gt; is an online event that runs between 2nd August 2019 and the 30th August 2019. There is a heap of awesome sponsors that you should out and a load of cool humans taking part as individuals and in teams registered on &lt;a href=&quot;https://getmakerlog.com/@theshawe&quot;&gt;makerlog&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you think this is cool and you want to throw a few universe dents my way. There are a few things you could do. The obvious thing to do is to share this post with a friend. Tell them about the &lt;a href=&quot;https://fixathon.io/&quot;&gt;fixathon&lt;/a&gt; and about how cool you think it is, raise the awareness of my entry and join &lt;a href=&quot;https://getmakerlog.com/@theshawe&quot;&gt;makerlog&lt;/a&gt; so you can learn about other entries, who they are and what they are doing. That’s the obvious thing. Other things that could be cool would be to listen to the podcast and subscribe to the RSS, Follow me on &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/theshawe&quot;&gt;twitter&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/theshawe&quot;&gt;@ me&lt;/a&gt; about the project, I’ll RT it and share your thoughts to my feed and lastly, if you want to help fund this project and my work on it I have set up a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.buymeacoffee.com/davidshawe&quot;&gt;Buy Me A Coffee Page&lt;/a&gt; where you can let me know that you think this is a really good idea by funding a payment my way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;lastly&quot;&gt;Lastly&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve set up a mailing list. So it would be great if you could sign up to that below!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Slán go fóill
Thank you, Cheers
David Shawe
Invisible Building&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://fixathon.io/&quot;&gt;fixathon.io&lt;/a&gt; |
&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.buymeacoffee.com/davidshawe&quot;&gt;buymeacoffee.com/davidshawe&lt;/a&gt; |
&lt;a href=&quot;https://getmakerlog.com/@theshawe&quot;&gt;getmakerlog.com/theshawe&lt;/a&gt; |
&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/theshawe&quot;&gt;twitter.com/theshawe&lt;/a&gt; |
&lt;a href=&quot;https://brew.com/ethicalchat&quot;&gt;brew.com/theshawe&lt;/a&gt; |
&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitch.tv/thetheshawe&quot;&gt;twitch.tv/theshawe&lt;/a&gt; |
&lt;a href=&quot;https://ethical.chat&quot;&gt;ethicalchat&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;a href=&quot;https://ethical.chat&quot;&gt;ethicalchat&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>theshawe</name></author><summary type="html">Introduction</summary></entry></feed>